<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO &#8211; JonathanBlog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/tag/personalized-wedding-anniversary-card-with-photo/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:15:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/android-chrome-512x512-3-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO &#8211; JonathanBlog</title>
	<link>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Best Deals! Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO</title>
		<link>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/best-deals-personalized-wedding-anniversary-card-with-photo/</link>
					<comments>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/best-deals-personalized-wedding-anniversary-card-with-photo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Anniversary Cards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/best-deals-personalized-wedding-anniversary-card-with-photo/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO Best Deals! Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO &#8211; Anniversary Cards This item is trending! Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO good product Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO You can order itDiamond Hearts Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO and NAME. 3 Sizes, Note Card, Standard (as shown) [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO</h4>
<p>Best Deals! Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO &#8211; Anniversary Cards This item is trending! <i>Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO</i>  good product  <b>Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO</b> You can order itDiamond Hearts Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO and NAME. 3 Sizes, Note Card, Standard (as shown) and Large or TRANSFER to your choice of THOUSANDS of other personalized wedding anniversary gifts. Beautiful Heart Shaped Diamond Designs on each side of Your Wedding or Anniversary Photo or Delete. You, or CALL Designer Linda: 239-949-9090 EST to CHANGE the Occasion, Year TRANSFER to a different Product. </p>
<p>For HELP, Design, Occasion, COLOR and Product CHANGES, Call or Text Designer Linda: 239-949-9090 EST to make Diamond wedding anniversary cards CHANGES or create more matching and coordinating personalized wedding anniversary presents, anniversary gifts for parents, grandparents, friend and your family. Wonderful as 70th anniversary cards, 75th anniversary cards, 60th diamond anniversary cards or ANY YEAR. Diamond Jubilee Cards or ANY OCCASIONS. </p>
<p>100% “LOVE IT” Guarantee. A+ BBB, Better Business Bureau Rating. </p>
<p>All designs are custom printed with various shades of colors to give it different looks, such as gold tones, silver, beveled looks, faux vintage designs, etc. Zazzle’s print on demand service is incredible. Vibrant, Detailed and Vivid shades of colors. </p>
<p>CALL or TEXT Zazzle Designer Little Linda Pinda: 239-949-9090 for HELP and Design, Color, Occasion, and Product CHANGES. We have thousands of different products, party supplies, device cases and so much more. Linda offers Custom designing service at No extra cost. I can also show you how to make design, and some color changes. Unique personalized party supplies, personalized gifts are shipped all over the world. North America, (US, Canada) UK, Australia, Europe, Asia, South America, etc…</p>
<p>Any part of any of any of my designs can be placed on your choice of thousands of customizable gifts, decor, accessories, apparel, party supplies, device cases and more.</p>
<p>Please SAVE Little Linda Pinda Designs Store LINKS and Telephone Number, below.<br />
Little Linda Pinda Designs offers you FREE Custom Designing Service.</p>
<p>Zazzle.com/Store/LittleLindaPinda</p>
<p><a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="84c8edf0f0e8e1c8edeae0e5d4edeae0e5c4e3e9e5ede8aae7ebe9">[email&#160;protected]</a>  * * * CALLING and TEXTING is Fastest.<br />
Subject Line “CONTACT LINDA”<br />
Calling and Texting is BEST and FASTEST</p>
<p>CALL or TEXT Little Linda Pinda at:<br />
239-949-9090 * EST 9 AM to 7 PM EST *</p>
<p>See more any year wedding anniversary ideas HERE:<br />
https://www.zazzle.com/littlelindapinda/gifts?cg=196050721621507373&amp;rf=238147997806552929 <b>Price:$4.17</b><br /><center> <center></p>
<h1><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2714.png" alt="✔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/personalized_wedding_anniversary_card_with_photo-256292157159894123?rf=238627982471231924">Best Deals! Personalized Wedding Anniversary Card with PHOTO ($4.17)</a> </h1>
<p></center> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/personalized_wedding_anniversary_card_with_photo-256292157159894123?rf=238627982471231924"><img decoding="async" src="https://rlv.zcache.com/personalized_wedding_anniversary_card_with_photo-r71ec4415963642d1a54d9ea20c52c7b1_udff0_500.jpg"></a></center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/best-deals-personalized-wedding-anniversary-card-with-photo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
