<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template &#8211; JonathanBlog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/tag/simple-chic-photo-birth-announcement-card-template/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:06:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/android-chrome-512x512-3-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template &#8211; JonathanBlog</title>
	<link>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Top 10! Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template</title>
		<link>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/top-10-simple-chic-photo-birth-announcement-card-template/</link>
					<comments>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/top-10-simple-chic-photo-birth-announcement-card-template/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Birth Announcement Cards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/top-10-simple-chic-photo-birth-announcement-card-template/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template Top 10! Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template &#8211; Birth Announcement Cards Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template quality over price Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template quality products and have the highest number of reviews in the same categoryOn the front, this simple, stylish [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template</h1>
<p>Top 10! Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template &#8211; Birth Announcement Cards <u>Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template</u> quality over price <i>Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template</i> quality products and have the highest number of reviews in the same categoryOn the front, this simple, stylish modern photo birth announcement template features your baby&#8217;s name with details beneath your photo along with your baby&#8217;s first name in a warm, expressive handwriting script near the top of the card that partially overlaps with the photo. If you prefer a more minimalist look, you can delete without replacing any of our sample stats on the front-you might not want to include the time of day or length, for example. And the length of your baby&#8217;s name above the stats might also prompt you to leave out some of the stats in order to achieve a balanced look between the two lines of text, etc. And speaking of balance, you might decide to make some of the front text larger or smaller. The default color for the text on the front is black, except for your baby&#8217;s name, which we&#8217;ve highlighted in an elegant gold tone called California Gold. We&#8217;ve included space for a photo on the back as well, and the back the default text color is black. You might choose to change the font, punctuation or color used for various text elements of this design on the front and/or back. For example, you might change the name or other text to blue, pink or a different color. We&#8217;ve chosen standard sharp corners as the default shape, but you can easily change that to rounded corners, as that look also works very well with this design. So check both styles and see which one grabs you! The default background on both sides is set as transparent to let the paper color simply serve as the base tone. But you can easily change this by either picking one of the basic colors in the editing tools, entering another color number in place of ours if you have a specific hue in mind that you found in your research, or by looking at the color spectrum tool and choosing something by sight. We&#8217;ve put some placeholder text on the back for you to delete and replace with your own message, with or without your names, if you want to sign by hand when you get the cards. But you might also simply choose to delete our placeholder text and leave the back entirely blank so that you can write a message by hand on each card and sign your names. The default paper type, matte, has a soft warmth to it and resists smudging, so it&#8217;s a great choice for writing your own message. You can edit this and choose semi-gloss or another paper type instead. In any case please do remember that there&#8217;s a second photo as well as placeholder text on the back as well and to delete all of our sample/placeholder text on both sides of the card and to replace both of the sample photos with your own. Use the intuitive design tools, your favorite photos and your inspiration to make this chic modern birth announcement card uniquely yours. We have a selection of other simply stylish modern baby arrival announcements, so please browse our store for more ideas! <b>Price:$2.34</b><br /><center> <center></p>
<h1>   <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/simple_chic_photo_birth_announcement_card_template-256205218105935669?rf=238627982471231924">Top 10! Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template ($2.34)</a> </h1>
<p></center> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/simple_chic_photo_birth_announcement_card_template-256205218105935669?rf=238627982471231924"><img decoding="async" src="https://rlv.zcache.com/simple_chic_photo_birth_announcement_card_template-r_vsedcb_500.jpg"></a></center></p>
<p> Category : Birth Announcement Cards</p>
<p></p>
<p> Tags : Top 10! Simple Chic Photo Birth Announcement Card Template</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jonathanblog.github.io/items/top-10-simple-chic-photo-birth-announcement-card-template/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
